Breakfast and Tiffany's
And bottles of bubbles
티파니에서 아침과 샴페인 한잔을
Girls with tattoos who
like getting in trouble
타투를 한 잘나가는 내 친구들과
Lashes and diamonds
ATM machines
속눈썹과 다이아몬드, 그리고 ATM기
Buy myself all of My favorite things
내가 좋아하는걸 다 사지
Been through some bad thing
I should be a sad soul
나쁜일을 많이 격었으니, 슬픔에 빠져 있었어야해
Who woulda thought It'd turn me to a savage
더 강해질 거라고 누가 생각했겠어
Rather be tied up with cuffs and not strings
남이 시키는대로 하느니 전화 받느라 바쁜게 더 나아
Write my own checks like I write what I sing
내가 가사를 쓰는 것처럼 수표를 써
My wrist, stop watching
내 손목좀 그만봐
My neck is flossin
내 목은 빛이나
Make big deposits
돈은 많이 있어
My gloss is poppin
내 입술은 빛이나
You like my hair? Gee thanks, just bought it
머리 맘에 들어? 고마워, 방금 한거야
I see it, I like it, I want it, I got it.
내가보고, 좋아하고, 가지고 싶으면 나는 다 가져
I want it, I got it
내가 원하면, 나는 가져
You like my hair? Gee thanks, just bought it
머리 맘에 들어? 고마워, 방금 한거야
I see it, I like it, I want it, I got it.
내가보고, 좋아하고, 가지고 싶으면 나는 다 가져
Wearing a ring but ain't gon'be no " mrs".
반지는 있지만, 결혼반지는 아니야
Bought matching diamonds for 6 of my buddies
내 친구 6명과 다이아반지 맞춘거야
I'd rather spoil all my friends with my riches
내 돈으로 친구를 망치는게 더 나아
Think retail therapy my new addiction
쇼핑으로 스트레서 푸는 것에 중독된 거 같아
Who ever said money can't solve your problems
누군가 돈으로 문제를 해결할 수 없다고 했지
Must not have had enough money to solve 'em
그건 그냥 그 사람이 문제를 해결할 만큼 돈이 없는거야
They say, " which one" I Say, " nah, I want all of' em"
그들이 뭘 살거냐고 물으면 나는 다 산다고 말해
Happiness is the same price as red bottoms
행복은 루브탱 신발과 같은거야
My smile is beaming
My skin is gleaming
내 웃음도 빛이나고, 내 피부도 빛이나
The way it shine I know you 've seen it
어떻게 빛나는지, 너도 본 적 있잖아
I bought a crib just for the closet
나는 옷장용으로 집을 하나 샀어
Both his and hers I want it, I got it
여자건 남자건 내가 원하면 가져
I want it, I got it
내가보고, 좋아하고, 가지고 싶으면 나는 다 가져
You like my hair? Gee thanks, just bought it
머리 맘에 들어? 고마워, 방금 한거야
I see it, I like it, I want it, I got it
내가보고, 좋아하고, 가지고 싶으면 나는 다 가져